To solve 2097152 matrixes of size 2, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 3.873792 ms
To solve 1048576 matrixes of size 4, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 5.097120 ms
To solve 524288 matrixes of size 8, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 6.308160 ms
To solve 262144 matrixes of size 16, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 7.574528 ms
To solve 131072 matrixes of size 32, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 8.782880 ms
To solve 65536 matrixes of size 64, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 8.519680 ms
To solve 32768 matrixes of size 128, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 9.298304 ms
To solve 16384 matrixes of size 256, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 9.800512 ms
To solve 8192 matrixes of size 512, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 10.838336 ms
To solve 4096 matrixes of size 1024, using the PCR algorithm, the time taken was : 11.901856 ms

To solve 2097152 matrixes of size 2, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 1.059744 ms
To solve 1048576 matrixes of size 4, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 2.022592 ms
To solve 524288 matrixes of size 8, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 6.233408 ms
To solve 262144 matrixes of size 16, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 13.789152 ms
To solve 131072 matrixes of size 32, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 18.109695 ms
To solve 65536 matrixes of size 64, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 20.861120 ms
To solve 32768 matrixes of size 128, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 31.329760 ms
To solve 16384 matrixes of size 256, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 37.610016 ms
To solve 8192 matrixes of size 512, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 38.607265 ms
To solve 4096 matrixes of size 1024, using the Thomas algorithm, the time taken was : 34.621086 ms

